gaurav bhatt

Web Developer | Software Developer

bgaurav015@gmail.com https://gauravb12.github.io/ 9915791315, 9451476737 Panjab University, Chandigarh

EDUCATION

UIET, Panjab University, Chandigarh

B.E. Information Technology (7.66/10) July 2015 - June 2019

MG Inter College, Gorakhpur, UP

Intermediate (88.6%) April 2014

MG Inter College, Gorakhpur, UP

HighSchool (85.6%) April 2012

SUMMARY

An IT undergraduate, with 2+ years of experience in Web and Software design to development. Have keen interest in Computers and Algorithms, and love to solve such problems. Have worked as research intern in Machine Learning based Object Detection. Looking forward to some more interesting experience!

EXPERIENCE

DIC, Panjab University

Summer Internship Worked on 'Pedestrian Detection Using Thermal Imaging' employing ML June 2017 - July 2017

Gandhi Bhawan. PU

Web Developer Developed the website for Gandhi Bhawan, Panjab University May 2017

ScholarX.org

Virtual Internship Back-End developer for ScholarX.org (Medical Student's online network) Feb 2017 - March 2017

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS
JS, jQuery
PHP, Node.JS
MySQL, MongoDB
C, C++
Python
Linux (Ubuntu)

LANGUAGE

Hindi (native)
English (proficient)

INTERESTS

Photography Blogging Music (vocals)

SELECTED PROJECTS

Lab Store System

Created a Lab Equipment's issue and return system on Node.JS and MongoDB for College Robotics Lab April 2017

GST offline system

Created a Node.JS and File System based application to generate JSON file required for GST return filing Dec 2017 - Jan 2018

CONFERENCES AND ACHIEVEMENTS

- Attended the 'Wiki to Learn Conference', LNMIIT, Jaipur. (Jan 2017)
- Won Hackathon (Fidelity theme), at TerraTechnica 2017. NIT Delhi
- Participated in the 'Innovative Design Contest', under DIC, UIET, PU held in Sep 2017.

POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILITY

MagBoard

• Graphic Designer, 2015-17.

Goonj 2016

- Member, Publicity Committee
- Graphic Designer (Literary Events)

HackSprint V1.0

• Organising team, HackSprint V1.0, Nov 2016

Tech Workshop

• Organiser, Workshop on Data Analysis & Swarm Robotics, Feb 2017

Izaad

• Chief Designer, Izaad, the LitFest, 2017